- [Sandy] Are you a React developer?
If yes, you are probably familiar
with the React API and its core concepts,
and chances are that you've run
into the must common programming problems,
like state management,
which is a big challenge for React developers.
Working on web projects requires multiple
and important considerations,
and it is essential for any developer
to understand software design
and architecture to build robust and efficient web projects.
Whether you're a beginner or a mid-level React developer,
this class is for you.
React state management is designed
to teach you how to manage the state of your app effectively
to guarantee the success of your web projects.
My name is Sandy.
I'm a senior software developer and a web trainer.
Join me to understand
and master the art of React state management.